{
    "id": "c926343b2a0744149003ddb601f85415",
    "title": "Such And So",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "ea351f8a9b2d4afeb3d9a808c6e52c5b",
            "title": "Such And So",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "You are ……………………… baby.",
                    "description": "We use such before a noun with or without an adjective.",
                    "answers": [
                        "such a",
                        "such",
                        "so",
                        "so a"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I am surprised that you have ………………….. patience.",
                    "description": "We use such before abstract nouns.",
                    "answers": [
                        "such",
                        "such a",
                        "so"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "She is ……………………… beautiful.",
                    "description": "We use so before an adjective.",
                    "answers": [
                        "such",
                        "such a",
                        "so"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "They are …………………….. idiots.",
                    "description": "We use such before plural nouns.",
                    "answers": [
                        "such",
                        "such an",
                        "so"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "She has got ……………………….. bizarre habits.",
                    "description": "We use such before plural nouns.",
                    "answers": [
                        "such",
                        "such a",
                        "so"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I have never met …………………….. beautiful woman.",
                    "description": "We use such a before a singular countable noun.",
                    "answers": [
                        "such",
                        "such a",
                        "so"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "She is ……………………… childish.",
                    "description": "Before adjectives, we use so.",
                    "answers": [
                        "such",
                        "so",
                        "such a"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "She has got ………………………. crazy ideas.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "such",
                        "such a",
                        "so"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "She is ………………………. intelligent.",
                    "description": "We use so before adjectives.",
                    "answers": [
                        "such",
                        "such an",
                        "so"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "It was …………………….. loud noise that it woke everybody.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "such",
                        "such a",
                        "so"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "I am glad that you are feeling …………………… better.",
                    "description": "We cannot use so before a comparative adjective. Instead, we use so much.",
                    "answers": [
                        "so",
                        "such",
                        "so much"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "We have got ………………………. to do.",
                    "description": "We can use much or so much before an infinitive. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "so",
                        "so much",
                        "such"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}